http://freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com/2006/11/privacy-policy.html

Free Blogger Templates
Here I designed simple blogger templates for you.It's free to use.You must leave a link to my website. Alteration not allowed.
14.11.06
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at rg_venkat@rediffmail.com.At freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com and how it is used.Site TrackingWe have a simple web statistics program running that tracks how many times each page is visited. When you visit a page, information is logged that contains your domain name , date, time, and pages visited. There is no personally identifiable information. The information we collect is:- Used to improve the content on our site- Never shared with other organizations for commercial purposesCurrently freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com uses the following third-party visitor tracking tools:- http://www.sitemeter.com.DoubleClick DART Cookie.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site..:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet..:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htmlSome of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....Google AdsenseThese third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and inks that appear on freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons )may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.freeblogger-templates.blogspot.com 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
Previous Posts
Blue Simple Template
Chocolate Template
Simple Template
Blogger Template : 1
Subscribe toPosts [Atom]
Original Design : freewpthemes.net
by www.freewpthemes.net Released Under Creative common licence
Blogger Templates @ Blogger Templates
Privacy Policy
